Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Wait here.
He told me to wait outside.
Let's go.
Why are you two still breathing?
We arrived after...
So I make sure I understand.
You came here.
Alone.
To this vineyard. in Sicily.
For?
You know who I am. then?
Yet you came anyway.
Why?
How did you find me?
No one ever has.
Okay.
Here you are.
Except you're a few meters short...
of what you came for.
We all end up where we're supposed to be.
Stop. stop. stop.
It's only you?
Okay. good.
Stay in the truck. son.
The blood pressure is very low.
He wouldn't have made it to the hospital.
He's about to go into shock.
Take a blanket and put it on his legs.
Mind the light. Thank you.
Thank you. That's good.
- Gio.
- Yes.
This man fell down.
He didn't fall. They shot him.
You brought me a man that fell down. Okay?
- Clean his wound here.
- Yes.
Lucky it was only a .22 caliber.
Gio saved your life.
So I ask...
did he save a good man?
Or a bad man?
Where are you headed?
Home.
Not so fast now.
Your wound...
it needs time to heal.
Will the bad men come looking for you?
Where am I?
Go slowly. okay?
Khalid. bring me the red snappers.
Coming.
Good morning.
A tea?
The tea bag.
Tea bag.
I'll bring it right away.
I'm sorry.
but tea is for old ladies and Englishmen.
Good morning.
Good morning. Aminah.
Gabby. I have
a small something for you. Come.
Go slowly.
Dad. Mum is calling you from the kitchen.
Your salad.
Enjoy it.
My name is Aminah.
Nice to meet you.
Excuse me. sir.
This shirt would look good on you!
This shirt is perfect.
It's your color.
With these pants.
What do you think?
Perfect outfit.
Okay. only one shirt.
but with the right pants.
Only one for me.
And the hat.
because it matches the shirt.
They are the same color.
Okay?
Marco. I needed to repair the freezer.
I have no business without it.
And what do I care about the freezer?
I'll pay you next week. Don't worry.
Come on. Angelo. give me the money.
Angelo. everyone must pay.
We've known each other
for a long time. right?
See you next week.
There is no problem. Angelo.
Really no problem.
Calm down. Good boy.
Pull yourself together.
Come on. let's go. Come on!
Khalid. let's get back to work.
Angelo!
Next week.
Don't piss me off.
Wait here.
Where's my brother?
Upstairs dealing with something.
These are the waivers. Sign them.
You cannot throw people
out of their homes. Do you understand?
These people don't know where to go.
Lucia.
Mr. Quaranta.
We cannot sign these papers.
Okay?
A court will decide.
And maybe you'll have
to find another building for your hotel.
I really hope you understand.
Thank you for your time.
Got a new car?
How's the new kid doing?
Good. He listens to me.
He'll be a good one.
Get everyone out.
So?
- I look out for you. don't I?
- Yes.
You're my brother and I love you.
but don't piss me off.
Make collections. Don't be loud about it.
I have more important issues.
Why don't you make me part
of these important things?
These are big ones.
Stay in your place.
You do what you do.
I have big plans for you.
Really?
Don't worry.
Leave him there.
for everyone to see.
Quick! Come on. Move it.
Quickly! Come on.
You're not supposed to smell the fish.
Look at the eyes.
Eyes are bright. Not cloudy.
Gills red or pink.
She's right.
I see Stefano finally sold that hat.
I like the hat. I like it.
- Two?
- How much is it?
Today you don't have to pay.
You are a friend of Enzo. You don't pay.
No. You are a friend of Enzo.
Enzo's friend. I can't let you pay.
Next time. I promise I'll let you pay.
Come on. Khalid. let's give him his fish.
Brother.
Been praying?
I don't think God is listening.
What's up?
It's time. little brother.
to help me with bigger issues.
I need you to put more pressure
on this town. these people.
We have big plans for Altamonte.
resorts. hotels. casinos.
You know what's to be done.
Sure. Vincent.
This entire coast will be ours soon.
All of it.
Calm. calm.
Calm down. Angelo. We're here to help you.
They destroyed all we have.
Hello. good morning.
Marshal Bonucci. Altamonte Carabinieri.
I need information...
on the owner of a van...
Ford...
blue or black.
Suspicion of arson.
Good for tea.
Hello?
Your daughter left school early.
Who is this?
Miss Marta.
Have you seen Gabby?
One of your officers picked her up
a while ago.
Is everything all right?
Daddy. Daddy.
He made a dumb mistake. Right?
He made a call he wasn't supposed to.
Stop!
I beg you!
You don't think we have friends there?
Why do you need to be difficult.
Carabiniere?
You know you shouldn't make trouble.
- Viking! Grab the kid. quick.
- I'm eating.
Who gives a shit you're eating.
Sure. we should all wait
for the Viking to finish eating!
Move it!
This will teach you a lesson.
Come on. bring her here.
Look at me!
Next time we'll hurt the little girl.
Or we do something worse. Got it?
We do something worse!
- Let her go!
- You shut up!
Good Carabiniere.
Hi. Marshal.
How are you?
What a pretty girl you are.
Remember me?
How's your head. Marshal? Does it hurt?
Don't worry. okay?
Marshal. listen.
I need a favor from you.
I need you to go to the Somalis...
and ask them for their boats.
Can you do that?
Sure. you can do that.
You're my message boy now. Marshal.
Bravo. Marshal!
Did you get what he said?
He's getting ready. He's fun!
Sit down.
Sit!
Go away! Go away. now!
Slowly.
Get the van.
This fucking American.
He meddles.
Give me the cigarette.
What do you want to do. Marco?
I'm gonna execute that motherfucker.
And Vincent?
Fuck Vincent.
He doesn't tell me what to do.
Let's go. Give me your gun.
Give me the gun. Understand?
We found packages in the back of the van.
Some kind of drug.
Not the usual.
Gonna send some techs down here
to go through it.
That the explosion at the train station
is the result
of an as-yet-unclaimed terrorist attack.
At the moment there are no suspects.
We are at your disposal.
You interrupted my breakfast.
I'm sorry about your brother.
Thank you.
Take a seat.
There is a matter
that I have to talk to you about.
Not today.
The CIA arrived.
They are looking for a terrorist cell
importing a jihad drug
and selling it across the EU.
Then take care of it.
You need to shut everything down.
There is a woman...
she's smart.
She'll figure out
that it wasn't the terrorists...
but it was you.
The Camorra...
buying drugs from the enemy...
and selling them on our own streets
to finance your enterprises.
You have to do your job.
Did you see what they did
with the money you paid them?
Did you see how many people died
in that train station attack?
Our people.
If I wasn't buying their drugs...
somebody else would have...
and the same people would be dead.
I'll take care of the woman.
You make sure nothing touches me.
So you understood nothing.
Nothing.
You're right.
I don't give a shit.
My brother is dead
and you're here talking about bullshit.
Without any information.
Are you stupid?
Or have you forgotten your place?
My place...
is head of the police.
Did you forget who you are?
You were a barbarian...
and a barbarian you'll always be.
I warned you.
- Where are you going?
- Stay here.
You must find who killed my brother.
Piece of shit! Understood?
Shut up!
Now my barbarians will bring you
to the hospital.
Hurry up and maybe one day
you'll wiggle a couple of fingers.
Did you get my message?
Next time I'll take your head
and mail it to your grandchildren.
Appreciate you giving us
a hand on this. Barella.
Let's go. Antonio.
My brother was murdered on your streets!
Bring me who did it...
and I will reward you!
You know who did it.
Tell me who killed my brother!
Next time it'll be more than your ear.
How many will I kill today?
Say who killed my brother...
or I'll kill your family while you watch.
You don't have to do this. my son.
- Really?
- Vincent.
Then shoot me too!
Then kill me!
We gotta go.
They're recording us. Vincent.
Let her go.
I'll kill you all!
Boss. we've got to go.
The police are coming.
Let's go!
What do we know about the American?
Nothing.
No one is talking.
We checked also with our contacts but...
nothing.
No one is talking?
Could be FBI. the CIA...
Interpol...
We don't know. Vincent.
What if it's one of our enemies.
one of the other families?
We will kill the American.
we will burn that fucking place!
Tomorrow. Simone.
Tomorrow.
What the fuck?
Go check.
Nothing.
There's no one there.
We all have to face...
Death.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm